[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first recorded successful operation to separate a pair of conjoined twins took place in this year.", "correct_answer": "1689", "incorrect_answers": ["1889", "1976", "1989"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does the majority of nutrient absorption take place?", "correct_answer": "small intestine", "incorrect_answers": ["mouth", "liver", "large intestine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "High School Musical was released in 2005.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What infection\u2019s symptoms are tiny white-headed pimples, usually at the base of hair shafts?", "correct_answer": "Folliculitis", "incorrect_answers": ["Impetigo", "Cellulitis", "Boils"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the EU founding members is the country of Libert\u00e9, \u00c9galit\u00e9, Fraternit\u00e9?", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["UK", "Germany", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1999 film Ravenous, Captain Boyd (Guy Pierce) resorts to eating Colonel Hart (Jeffrey Jones) to stay alive.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Australian animal is the largest living carnivorous marsupial on Earth?", "correct_answer": "The Tasmanian devil", "incorrect_answers": ["The Tasmanian tiger", "The platypus", "The red kangaroo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first US city to play a Beatles song on the radio?", "correct_answer": "Seattle", "incorrect_answers": ["Pittsburgh", "Memphis", "Cleveland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress portrayed Catwoman in the 1992 movie Batman Returns?", "correct_answer": "Michelle Pfeiffer", "incorrect_answers": ["Meg Ryan", "Nicole Kidman", "Kim Basinger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mayday, an emergency code word used internationally as a distress signal, derives from which language?", "correct_answer": "French", "incorrect_answers": ["German", "English", "Italian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alopecia is the medical term which refers to baldness.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which species of Smilodon was the largest?", "correct_answer": "Smilodon populator", "incorrect_answers": ["Smilodon fatalis", "Smilodon locor", "Smilodon gracilis"]}]